free-php-webhosting.com 2009-06-22

# Privacy Policy

## free-php-webhosting.com Privacy Policy

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your ISP and to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes.  
This site contains links to other sites. Free-php-webhosting.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, services, and products. We collect visitor's contact information (like their e-mail address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, income level, or age). Contact information from the order form is used to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers.

The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

#### COOKIES

We use an outside ad company to display advertisements on our site. These advertisements may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.

Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our websites (and third party websites). To prevent cookies being placed on your computer please disable them in your browser's options. Consult your web browser's documentation and Wikipedia for more information:  
<http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_beacon>  
<http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>

#### ADVERTISING

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our service, this may change without prior notification being served. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

#### PUBLIC FORUMS

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### SECURITY

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

#### CHOICE/OPT OUT

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can contact us at the support system in your control panel.

#### CORRECT/UPDATE

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

You can contact us at the support system in your control panel.

#### CONTACTING THE WEBSITE

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, You can contact us at The support system in your control panel.
  *[IP]: Internet Protocol
  *[ISP]: Internet service provider
